NAOMI MEININGER

nmeining18@gmail.com | 201.957.3868 | www.linkedin.com/in/naomi-meininger | https://github.com/naomi-meininger | https://g

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Engineer at Disney Streaming with internship experience at Major League Baseball and Blue Cross Blue Shield. Proven leader in projects with Tufts TAMID and a background in teaching computer science, leveraging a diverse skill set in programming, data analysis, and network security.

EXPERIENCE

Disney Streaming, Software Engineer I

Nov 2024 - Present

Major League Baseball, Test Engineering Intern

lune 2024 - Aug 2024

- Implement **Playwright** tests for the MLB homepage and Home Run Derby Bracket using **JavaScript**, **GraphQL**, **Forge CMS**, **Apollo**, and **React**
- Develop integration tools for **TestRail** and **Slack** to upload **Playwright** test results directly to the platforms, utilizing **GitHub Actions**, the **TestRail API**, the **Slack API**, and **JUnit**
- Streamline automated testing for the All Star Ballot by adding data-testids to the React codebase

Blue Cross Blue Shield of Massachusetts, Full Stack Software Engineering Intern

June 2023 - Aug 2023

- Utilize Spring Boot, Selenium, Java, and Python to scrape LogRocket data and store it in PostgreSQL
- Develop a Random Forest Model to predict top 3 links for 5 insurance plans
- Create an **Angular Service** with **Python** backend to display links on BCBSMA homepage
- Enhance security and integrate endpoints using **Spring Boot**, **Python**, and **Angular** in MyBlue developer tools

Tufts TAMID, President, Co-Director of Data Science Sector, Associate Data Scientist

Oct 2020 - April 2024

- Manage consulting, finance, data science, and budgeting while coordinating projects, membership, and sector education
- Apply knowledge of data science, including deep neural networks and decision trees, to real-world projects

Tufts University, Teaching Assistant for Computer Science

Aug 2021 - May 2024

- Conduct student instruction on recursion, pointers, and functional programming
- Manage office hours, grade assignments, lead a 26-person lab, and contribute to course infrastructure

Girls Who Code, Teaching Assistant for Summer Immersion Program

May 2022 – Aug 2022

- Teach HTML, CSS, and JavaScript while fostering sisterhood and promoting female representation in STEM

SKILLS

Programming Languages: C++, C, Python, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Typescript, PHP, LaTex, SQL

Libraries and Frameworks: Node, Angular, Spring Boot, Flask, React, Apollo, Forge CMS, GraphQL, npm, Yarn

Databases and APIs: PgAdmin, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Coding and Hosting Platforms: VsCode, Google Colab, Jupyter Notebook, SiteGround, Heroku

Software Tools: Selenium, Beautiful Soup, Git, Gitlab, Jira, Confluence, TestRail, Playwright, JUnit, AWS, HPC, GitHub Actions

Network Security Tools: Wireshark, Nmap, Netcat, Scapy, Shodan, John the Ripper, Hashcat, Sqlmap, Burp Suite, apktool

Data Science and Machine Learning: Scikit-learn, Pandas, Tensorflow **Non-Native Languages:** Professional Working Spanish, Beginner Italian

PROIECTS

Alarm (Python, Scapy)

- Develop a network incident detection tool that enables users to identify potential vulnerabilities and security breaches in network traffic using **live network streams** and **sets of PCAP files** for various security incidents

Theta Budget Tracker (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, Selenium, Python)

- Build a sorority budget management platform using **Flask** for the backend, **Selenium** for budget scraping, and **Heroku** for deployment

EDUCATION

Tufts University

Sept 2020 - May 2024

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, Minors in Mathematics and Theater, Magna Cum Laude

INTERESTS

Musical Theater, Disney, Sousaphone, Trivia, Community Outreach